[Music]
Hey listen, what did I tell you that you're going from house to
house collecting tolls? What did I steal? What did I
steal? It's as if you don't know anything. You're acting like
Sati Savitri. You're like a
sugar candy. You're our Mohammed.
Otherwise, I'll take my monthly allowance and go inside. Go away. Otherwise, what are you doing?
Mania, what are you doing?
Eat meat. What's going on?
Everyone, come inside and see. The woman has come to fight.
Husband, eat meat. Come on, mother, come, if she bites you, you'll get
cancer. Go away. Hey,
Pragya, what's going on? Areniya is going from house to house collecting toll.
Hey, brother, take care of her. Hey,
brother, I'm taking care of her. You take her away.
One day, she'll go straight to the community. Come,
kill her. I'm waiting to get killed. Come,
let me go. I'll tell her today. Come on, friend, I wo
n't go inside. When she's
not scared, why should I be scared? Go fight, [ __ ].
Come on, brother, let's have a party. If she can have her way,
we both can.  Childhood friendship will get you
[ __ ]
[music] Let the
sister-in-law fight, when she cools down she will go away
[music]
[music] The
sister-in-law is dead, the force has been averted
[laughter]